It 's a little girl , my lady .
She 's beautiful .
My baby .
Poor little creature .
I 'd like to see you grow .
But you must survive .
Take her to the convent . Please promise you 'll protect her .
And don 't let them take her .
Swear . Swear .
I swear . I will protect her .
I 'll take her to the convent .
Justine , at last you 're here .
This way Justine .
We were so sorry to hear about your parents ' death .
We 've been expecting you for several days now .
Come on .
Come on !
Here she is , Justine .
Yes Mother Superior , I know Danielle has been very happy here with you .
- Excuse me mother . - That 's alright .
They were just leaving .
Now young lady , I hope you will not forget us .
No of course not . She 'll be back again next summer .
You 've done wonders and soon she 'll be able to do things for herself .
Won 't you darling ?
I 'm sorry I can 't stay , but we have to get back to the village .
Patients get restless you know .
Mother ... This is Justine .
- Reverend Mother . - Now child .
There 's nothing to be afraid of . Life must go on .
What you need now is rest .
- Is the room ready Sister Angelica . - Yes Mother .
Remember Justine . From now on , this is your home .
- Sister Angelica will show you the way . - Thank you .
You will find a new life here Justine .
Come along .
Now you have to think of yourself .
Remember the Lord will always be here to guide you . And so will I.
Come right this way Justine . This is your room .
Let me open the window to let in some fresh air and sun .
And this ... is your bed .
Now promise me you 'll try to get some rest .
- We 'll call you in time for supper . - Thank you Sister .
- Justine . - Yes ?
I hope you 'll be happy here . But if ever you 're in need or troubled
Please don 't hesitate to call on me . Alright ?
Thank you , Sister .
Hello .
I 'm Alucarda .
- My name is Justine . - Who 's that ?
My mother and my father .
- Mother just died . - I never met my mother or my father .
- I 'm sorry . - I 've got something to show you too .
These are things I never show anyone . They 're secret .
Every day I find a new secret . Look .
Look at all this . It belongs to me .
This for instance .
It means I like you .
And this .
Do you know how small creatures love each other ?
No .
I 'll show you . I 'll take you to the gardens , to the woods .
Everything is there .
What 's that ?
I 've never seen anything like them before .
It 's one more secret .
One is identical to the other .
It 's like an image in a mirror .
Like you and me .
Do you want us to be sisters ?
Come on . Come on .
Look .
They are burying a sister . She killed herself .
They will bury her in unhallowed ground .
I 'm afraid of funerals .
We have to die . All of us has to die .
And there 's no way we can avoid it .
Don 't be afraid .
It 's not very far .
Come on .
Well , well , well . What have we here ?
Would you like to see ... Oh , please .
Please don 't be afraid of me . I was just in the middle of an interesting game .
Would you like to know what it is ?
I think we should start back .
Would you like to know how someone will die .
Or would you like to buy an amulet ?
Which will bring good luck . Lots , lots .
I have many more things myself , in these woods .
Follow . Don 't be afraid . Follow .
Come on .
No .
Come on . He won 't hurt us .
Justine !
Alucarda !
Don 't believe such a creature . He 'll only tell you lies .
Better let me read your hand .
- Oh , my God ... - What did you see ?
Nothing . Perhaps a reflection of her own dreams .
I see nothing . Only shadows ...
Take care .
She 's yours .
Sell her your charms for the supernatural .
Look at the marvelous things that I have .
Among other things I profess the useful art of alchemy . I can turn dust
into precious stones .
and these , in dreams never imagined .
And you , young lady . Look .
This knife was the tear of a gypsy girl .
What strange eyes this girl has . Deep , sharp ,
mysterious . As the birds in the forest .
I see clearly . Your past and future , your dreams .
You 've come from the dew in the forest and there they will be waiting for you .
Strange creatures they are , and you must take care .
If it obsesses the young lady , here I am and here is my box of charms .
If she wishes I will make her free from such a dream .
then if the dream comes true , I shall be expecting her .
Hey , where are you going ?
Did I offend her ?
Alucarda ! Alucarda , wait .
Look .
It looks so familiar .
- Let 's go inside . - No ! This place scares me .
Let 's go back .
Are you afraid ? Justine
This is simply beautiful .
Come .
I hear the voices from the past .
I feel as if I 've been here before . I remember every stone and branch .
It 's as if I lost this world a long time ago .
One can live eternally instead of turning into a little pile of dust .
Are you ...
- Are you afraid of dying ? - Yes .
Everyone is .
I mean dying , loving each other . Dying together , to live as one forever .
With the same blood always flowing through our veins .
Darling . Darling Justine .
I live in you . Would you die for me ?
I love you so .
I have never been in love with anyone . And never shall .
Unless it 's with you .
- Do you mean that ? - You 're quite right to ask .
You don 't know how dear you are to me . I hope you love me as I love you .
Call me cruel and selfish , but love is always selfish .
You don 't know how jealous I am . I want you to love me to death .
Alucarda , for the love of God , Don 't talk to me of death .
I have a dream . The memory of a night .
I was almost murdered . Wounded here .
I was never the same again .
- Were you near death ? - Very close .
Let 's make a pact .
If we ever depart from this life , we shall do it together .
We shall do it together ,
Alright . If it makes you happy .
No , Alucarda !
Wait .
Lucille died in 1850 .
15 years ago Justine .
Our age . See what 's there .
I 'm afraid Alucarda .
- Let 's open it . - No .
My God !
I told you this place frightened me . Look what it 's done to you .
Please let 's go back .
It 's cold . I 'm shivering .
We have to Go back .
Go back . Go back !
The devil enters the body of the person he wants to control .
Uses the organs of that body for his own pleasure .
And performs feats , far above the capacity , strength
and ability of the person thus possessed .
Here in the holy book
for the knowledge of mankind ,
since the days of our lord , and even before , Satan and the other demons
have persecuted the souls of Christians .
they make no distinction between men , women and children .
He , the devil , uses the bodies of others as his own ,
destroying those he wants to dominate .
Perverting their language and distorting their lips .
Froth exits their mouths rather than words .
Lead a virtuous life and place yourselves in the hands of Our Lord .
You must live within the rules of our religion .
The only true religion . Otherwise
the devil will find a place inside our bodies
and take our souls away . And then ...
we shall burn in hell forever .
Throughout eternity . Your souls will find no rest .
Your bodies will suffer eternal torture .
The wrath of Satan has no mercy . Repent !
Oh , God , please help me . I don 't want to burn in hell .
Calm down .
Justine , what 's wrong . Answer me .
Are you feeling better now ? What happened ?
I don 't know .
She shouldn 't be left alone .
She should rest for a while .
I can look after her .
Please don 't leave me alone .
I can stay with her .
Would you like to stay Alucarda ?
Alright .
We 'll leave her in your care , Alucarda .
If you need anything , I won 't be far .
Monsters ! Monsters ! They have done this to you .
Justine . Don 't tell of our secret .
I hear voices . Voices from the past .
The same dark voices . They were soft at first .
I was looking at the trees
and the voices began to speak to me .
Coming from the forest . I can hear them clearly Justine .
Only you and me . Only you and me Justine .
My God , I 'm so scared .
We will make them pay . Bit by bit . For all they have taken away from us .
Alucarda .
Lucifer . Lucifer .
Satan ! Lucifer !
Alucarda , for God 's sake .
What 's happening ?
Please !
Alucarda , please stop it .
Death ! Death ! Death !
- Death . - Alucarda . Please , no .
Alucarda . Answer me .
Answer me , please . Answer me .
We 'll make a pact and seal it with our blood .
We 'll make them pay .
You 're right . We 'll make them pay .
To start with , a little rain .
Thunder !
Call him . Call him . Call him !
Lucifer ! Satan !
Look at me . You 're so beautiful , Justine .
Look at me . Look at me .
Now you shall blend . One with the other .
one with the other . And then ...
blend into me .
Look at me , dear Justine .
Welcome Justine .
Giver of all gifts . Of flowers and fruits .
Jesus. give me strength .
Please .
Behold the body of thy new servant .
My Lord .
Don 't abandon me .
Manifest your spirit . Satan ... Lucifer .
Do not abandon me Lord .
We beseech thee , Satan .
God !
Save Justine .
Don 't abandon her Lord .
Please keep her from harm .
Today we will continue studying the teachings of Saint Theresa .
And this is what the devil does .
To beget his evil he obtains help from our virtues .
Even if the gain is small , his harvest is great .
But God in his infinite wisdom understands the wiles of the devil .
And so gives us the strength to face them with noble thoughts
and prayer . In this way ,
I trust that you have been listening .
Yes Sister .
Then you can repeat what I have just read .
Well , Alucarda ?
Stand up child .
And this is what the devil does .
He grants us virtues to expand his kingdom .
The only valid one .
God with his lack of knowledge does not understand this truth ,
and opposes it with false thoughts and prayers .
God . Silence !
Our lord and master . I acknowledge thee as my God and Prince .
I promise to serve and obey thee as long as I shall live .
I renounce the other God and all the saints .
Don 't listen , don 't listen to them .
Lord and master .
Don 't listen . Go out of the room .
Go , go , go .
I promise to do all that is evil .
I will declare you name to all and will not cease to serve the Lord of Darkness .
My body , my soul and my life belong to you .
Call the Mother Superior , quickly .
What 's wrong with you girls ?
God help up , please .
Please , stop it .
Alucarda , my child .
This is blasphemy .
Listen to me sisters . This is blasphemy . God help me .
How dare you blaspheme . Are you mad ?
Have you taken leave of your senses ? Answer me . Answer me .
I only repeated what you said .
God forgive you .
You have just invoked the kingdom of darkness
and rejected the infinite wisdom of God .
And now you deny it . And Alucarda too .
Liars . Repent . Here in front of the cross .
Beg . Ask for forgiveness .
- Sister Germana - Reverend Mother , thank god you 're here
I have to inform you of the strange and blasphemous behaviour of these girls
Mother , in front of me Sister Mary and all the pupils .
Justine and Alucarda denied the Lord our Christ .
They used the most evil language to recognise Satan as their Lord and Master
- I can 't believe it . - But it 's true .
What have you to say for yourself ?
Sister Mary .
Send for the doctor , perhaps they are ill .
Father Lazarus will be here soon .
I want them both to be prepared for confession .
- Go , hurry now . - Yes .
- I need more light . - She gets worse by the minute , doctor .
- How long has she been like this ? - Since this morning .
But she has got much worse .
Her pulse is faint .
Her heart is weak .
This girl is very sick .
Pray , Justine .
Pray , my child .
Pray for the sake of your soul .
Pray . Pray Justine . Pray .
What is it girl ? What 's the matter ?
Easy girl . Easy .
It is your turn now Alucarda .
- Yes my child . - I ... I ...
- Yes , go on . - I was told to come to you .
Speak up then .
I was asked to answer a question and I did .
And Sister Germana is angry with me .
And for a very good reason .
I am not what you may think father .
The facts were explained to me my child .
You have sinned .
I don 't recall doing anything wrong .
Liars rot in hell for eternity .
I know for sure that you are doing wrong .
Don 't miss this opportunity which has been granted you .
You can tell the truth here and now .
Perhaps I have done wrong .
I couldn 't have lied . I love life ... with
With ...
- Go on . - Justine .
is a close friend of mine . I love her .
You call yourself blessed , and believe in eternal life and worship God .
I worship life , you worship death .
I love Justine . You love to kill .
We have made a pact and sealed it with our blood .
Justine and I
The fault isn 't ours , but yours .
You cover your body with a black cassock as if you are ashamed of it .
But you 'd like to possess me wouldn 't you ?
Take me . Take off your cassock .
- What happened Father ? - What happened ?
Please sister , get her out of here .
My God , no ... no .
All we can do is wait .
We 'll know better tomorrow .
- I hope she 'll recover . - I 'm convinced she will
with the help of the Lord .
The things she said were so horrible .
Please Lord do not abandon us in such times of difficulty .
You did not hear what she said . It was the devil .
As if the devil himself was speaking through her mouth .
These words cannot come from anyone else , only the devil .
- The devil . - The devil .
Father Lazarus .
Do you really believe that because we belong to the church
we are safe from the devil 's influence ?
I remember when I visited the archives at the Vatican .
I read many incidents that had been confirmed .
Incidents like this .
In 1491 , at the monastery of Cameron some nuns became immensely strong .
They barked like dogs and predicted the future .
They contaminated the rest of the community ,
and made the monastery a temple of the devil .
In 1550 the nuns of the convent of Nazareth
became possessed .
They climbed trees like cats and levitated for hours .
In 1555 , in Rome itself ,
in an orphanage just like this one ,
three orphans were responsible for horrible things ,
which could only be the work of a diabolical mind .
Two of them became seriously ill .
And the third finally died , killing all three .
Justine and Alucarda may be possessed .
Mother
The devil is elsewhere , not in those poor girls .
It looks like we are the victims of a conspiracy .
Justine and Alucarda are possessed by the devil .
It 's not surprising that Satan
has chosen these delicate creatures .
His plans are directed against the Holy Church and its representatives .
They may not be possessed by the devil himself
but at least by one of his evil messengers .
What are we going to do ?
We must pray that God can help us . Jesus Christ
Deliver us from this nightmare . Don 't let them ...
possess us .
How long has Justine been like this ?
Almost a week . And then she became ill .
She fainted during the hymns and said the light affected her .
That 's it . A heliophobic demon .
A sixth category devil who hates light .
He acts at night , when the shadows protect him .
We must destroy him in order to free the girls .
We must prepare ...
an exorcism .
Justine . Poor Justine .
I won 't let them harm you . I won 't let them take you away .
I 'll take you somewhere where you can be safe .
My poor Justine . You 've got to help me .
- No . - You must get up .
Sister , what d 'you think you 're doing ?
Open the door .
Come child .
Do not despair my child .
We are here to deliver you from evil .
It 's not the child , but the demon inside her that 's resisting .
I shall prove this by exposing la marca diaboli .
The devil 's mark she has on her skin . The mark of the devil .
Remove her clothing .
God of heaven . Jesus Christ .
Die soon ! Die soon !
This is all the evidence I need . You have all seen her .
They cannot stand the name of our Saviour . They are possessed .
You 'll die soon !
Silence her .
I order thee , evil spirit
in the name of the one who judges .
the one who has created and can destroy the world ,
The one who has the power to send you to hell .
Go ! Depart !
Leave the bodies of these two servants of God .
They must return to the Holy Church .
By the power of my faith and of the Holy Ghost
I demand that you return to your bottomless pit .
Humble yourself at the feet of Christ , because his faith is greater than yours .
Christ before whom you tremble .
Christ who takes lost souls from the fires of hell , to the light of heaven .
Now depart . Back where you belong , evil spirit .
God commands you . Do not resist .
God the Father commands you
God the Son commands you
God the Holy Ghost commands you .
The Holy Cross commands you .
The faith of St. Peter and St. Paul commands you .
All the saints command you .
The Holy Cross commands you .
All the faithful command you .
Depart , seducer . Enemy of virtue .
Stop it .
Stop it , I say .
Doctor , how dare you interrupt our holy ritual .
Holy ritual . This is the most shameful thing I have ever witnessed .
This is not the fifteenth century .
I thought reason had replaced superstition .
This is not an act of faith .
This is the most primitive expression of ignorance I have ever seen .
You ...
You ... You have just killed Justine .
How dare you .
Damn you ! Damn you !
Release her .
I 'm taking this girl with me , before you kill her , as you killed Justine .
My Lord .
Oh , my Christ .
You were witness . How did this happen .
Where is the love he spoke of , Mother ?
To cleanse her spirit
you have destroyed her body .
But the Lord will not abandon her soul , because it is pure .
May he have mercy on you for all that you have done .
Enough Sister .
- Yes ? Who is it . - Open the door please .
- Doctor , what 's happened ? - She 's been hurt . We must care for her .
- How is she doctor ? - She 's alright . Bring the stethoscope .
It 's alright .
Don 't touch me .
Nobody wants to hurt you .
Everything 's alright .
Father ...
I 'm scared .
- Is anything wrong ? - It 's Alucarda .
She had a nightmare .
Don 't be scared , darling . She just had a nightmare .
Who is she ?
Don 't be afraid .
It 's only me .
Daniela . You just had a bad dream .
You 're safe with us . Try to rest now .
Can I stay with her for a little while father ?
Yes , darling , but not too long . I 'll be downstairs if you need me .
- Your father want to frighten me ? - He doesn 't Alucarda .
- You were dreaming . - I 'm afraid of dreams .
The things I see are so real .
My father is a good doctor . He 'll cure you .
- Have we ever met before ? - I don 't think so .
Because ...
I do remember people 's voices .
- You are very pretty . - And you are beautiful .
Please don 't go . Stay with me .
Rubbish , pure rubbish .
- Who is it . - It 's me doctor , Felipe .
Something terrible has happened at the convent .
- You 've got to come . - But it 's five in the morning .
The Reverend Mother sent me . You are to come right away .
I 'm familiar with the terrible things at the convent . What is it now ?
She didn 't say . Only that you had to come .
I 'll be right down .
Thank God you 've come , Dr. Hasley .
Justine 's shroud .
- Who did this ? - That 's what we would like to know .
She was brought here to be prepared for burial .
She was here all night , until a few hours ago .
- Who was with her ? - Sister Veronica .
- Where is she now ? - We don 't know doctor .
The least you should have done was to say with her yourself .
Doctor . Doctor , please .
No one in the convent has been sleeping since Justine died .
We have been flagellating ourselves as we flagellated Justine .
- Then someone took Justine 's body . - There 's no other explanation .
- I must notify the authorities . - No . They 'll want to know how she died .
- Our religious community . The scandal . - Don 't worry .
The death certificate will say Justine died of an unforeseen accident ,
which is partly true .
Doctor , Mother Superior , Doctor . Come quickly .
Oh , my God .
She 's been burned to death .
It looks as if the fires of hell have reached her .
Take her to the chapel .
I want to look at the corpse again .
- I 'll go with you . - No .
I want to examine it alone , if you don 't mind .
Take her to her cell .
Father , what is the meaning of this ?
This nun was dead , and yet ...
She moved .
The devil moved her limbs .
She was dead .
But the forces of evil had not abandoned her .
How can you explain this from a scientific point of view ?
It happened , is happening in front of your very eyes .
Do you still doubt ?
I don 't know .
You 're the only one here who has the answer .
These are the doings of the transgressor ,
The seducer , the enemy of virtue .
The perpetual persecutor of innocence .
The arch enemy of Almighty God .
You mean ... the devil ?
The devil .
I still can 't believe it .
And yet this destruction was by someone who hates all religious manifestation .
To that being , this chapel
was a terrible antagonist .
When I studied at the University of Paris , I was taught
that demonic possession was pure nonsense .
Or the sad result of the workings of an insane mind .
They taught me that religion was a farce and a form of slavery .
That the time has come to break the chains of superstition .
I 'm a man of reason .
And I 'm faced with something supernatural ,
which frightens me .
This woman was dead .
Yet there was evil inside her ready to come alive and attack the innocent .
This could only be as you say ,
the work of what you call the devil .
Yes . It was the devil , who entered our sister 's body .
And turned her from the altar of the Almighty to the fires of hell .
- Someone must have contaminated her . - Justine .
And we must find her ...
before there are more victims , more corpses , more possessed .
Yes , we must find Justine , or what is left of her .
You won 't believe how things were .
But that 's why we exorcised Justine and Alucarda .
They were possessed by the devil .
Is that why Alucarda was at the ceremony ?
Her behaviour was evil , diabolical .
- Oh , my God , no ... Daniela . - Doctor
Daniela 's alone with her .
Daniela .
Thank you father .
- Mother Superior . Daniela 's gone . - I understand .
We must find them immediately or Daniela also will be possessed .
- We 'll all search for them . - Thank you Mother .
- Are you ready Doctor ? - Yes Father .
We must find Alucarda . Where should we start looking ?
- I think I could help find her . - How would you know , sister Angelica .
I remember some of the places they used to go together .
- Let 's go then . - Promise me you won 't hurt her .
- Please Doctor . - Don 't worry .
This way doctor .
Mother Superior , please bring Father Lazarus .
- Yes doctor . - Sister Theresa , where 's your cross ?
I 've lost it .
Thank you sister .
Doctor .
They used to come here .
There seems to be another way out . Come on Brother Felipe .
Please , no !
Justine .
Oh , God . Justine .
You 're just killing her .
Doctor ... Alucarda ...
The convent .
Alucarda at the convent .
Of course . That would be the last place we would look for her .
She must be there .
Burn them .
Lucifer .
Doctor , what 's happening ?
Alucarda !
Take her out .
Satan .
Let it down .
Lucifer .
Alucarda , please .
Daniela .
God the Father commands thee .
God the Holy Ghost commands thee .
Subtitles : Corvusalbus